[

    {
        "question": "What surrounds the area where all of humanity lives?",
        "answers": [
            "Titans",
            "Police",
            "Marley",
            "Walls"
        ],
        "answer": "Walls"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the innermost wall?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Rose",
            "Wall Maria",
            "Wall Sheena"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Sheena"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the second outermost wall?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Maria",
            "Wall Sheena",
            "Wall Rose"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the outermost wall protecting the humans called?",
        "answers": [
            "Wall Rose",
            "Wall Sheena",
            "Wall Maria"
        ],
        "answer": "Wall Maria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which branch of the military protects the Royal Family?",
        "answers": [
            "Cadet Corps",
            "Scout Regiment",
            "Garrison Regiment",
            "Yeagerists",
            "Military Police Brigade"
        ],
        "answer": "Military Police Brigade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Eren's love interest?",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Historia",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa Ackerman"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa Ackerman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which family member does Eren watch get eaten by a Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Sister",
            "Father",
            "Best Friend",
            "Brother",
            "Mother"
        ],
        "answer": "Mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the story, who is the first human shown to be a Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Reiner",
            "Bertholdt",
            "Annie",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Eren's best friend?",
        "answers": [
            "Jean",
            "Connie",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which branch of the military tries to reclaim land from the Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Cadet Corps",
            "Garrison Regiment",
            "Military Police Regiment",
            "Scout Regiment"
        ],
        "answer": "Scout Regiment"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who ruined Eren's equipment back in the trainee days?",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Keith",
            "Jean",
            "Armin",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Keith"
    },
    {
        "question": "For how many years was ymir wandering outside the walls as a pure titan?",
        "answers": [
            "60 Years",
            "50 Years",
            "40 Years",
            "30 Years",
            "80 Years",
            "70 Years"
        ],
        "answer": "60 Years"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number is Eren's trainee squad in Attack on Titan?",
        "answers": [
            "101st",
            "103rd",
            "112th",
            "96th",
            "104th"
        ],
        "answer": "104th"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest a Titan can be?",
        "answers": [
            "1 meter",
            "5 meters",
            "7 meters",
            "1.5 meters",
            "3 meters"
        ],
        "answer": "3 meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a special power of the Colossal titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Steam Attack",
            "Hardening",
            "Endurance",
            "Call titans to its side"
        ],
        "answer": "Steam Attack"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is in charge of the defense of the southern region?",
        "answers": [
            "Erwin Smith",
            "Levi Ackerman",
            "Hange Zoe",
            "Dot Pixis"
        ],
        "answer": "Dot Pixis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nickname was given to Erwin when he was a child?",
        "answers": [
            "Smith",
            "Blondie",
            "Smartass",
            "Cold Eyes",
            "Eyebrows"
        ],
        "answer": "Eyebrows"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the race that can turn into Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Marleyan",
            "Eldians",
            "Devils of the Island",
            "Paradis",
            "Subjects of Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Subjects of Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Miche was the second strongest soldier in the Survey Corps behind Levi in skill",
        "answers": [
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the manga, Who is the first to see the Wall titan inside the wall?",
        "answers": [
            "Stohess Residents",
            "Hange Zoe",
            "Mikasa Ackerman",
            "Nick"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa Ackerman"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Wall Maria fall?",
        "answers": [
            "Year 825",
            "Year 849",
            "Year 845",
            "Year 840"
        ],
        "answer": "Year 845"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the names of Hange's captured titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Fang and Frank",
            "Jeff and Gavin",
            "Jaws and Claws",
            "Sawney and Beane"
        ],
        "answer": "Sawney and Beane"
    },
    {
        "question": "How tall is Eren's Attack titan?",
        "answers": [
            "20 meters",
            "18 meters",
            "15 meters",
            "12 meters"
        ],
        "answer": "15 meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a special trait/ability of the Attack titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Hardening",
            "Regeneration",
            "Fighting for freedom",
            "Able to see the future"
        ],
        "answer": "Able to see the future"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was ranked first in using ODM gear in the 104th trainee corps?",
        "answers": [
            "Jean",
            "Mikasa",
            "Reiner",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Jean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was not among the top 10 graduates?",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Historia",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are pure titans active in the night?",
        "answers": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the 13th Commander of the Scout Regiment?",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Erwin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Shoving a sword up a titan's ass is another way to kill it",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Levi's mom's name?",
        "answers": [
            "Olympia",
            "Kara",
            "Karol",
            "Kuchel"
        ],
        "answer": "Kuchel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What profession did Levi's mom have before Levi was born?",
        "answers": [
            "Waitress",
            "Prostitute",
            "Nurse",
            "Soldier"
        ],
        "answer": "Prostitute"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is Mikasa's scarf in the manga",
        "answers": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Black",
            "White"
        ],
        "answer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the manga's extra pages, The buildings that were destroyed were 21st centurary buildings while the ones in the anime credits are futuristic",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Isayama's inspiration for the Titans?",
        "answers": [
            "Zombies",
            "Children",
            "Drunks",
            "Aliens"
        ],
        "answer": "Drunks"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many titan's has Eren killed as a human?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "3",
            "8",
            "1"
        ],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wall titans are 60 meters tall",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first to get eaten in the trainee corps by a titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Nack",
            "Franz",
            "Daz",
            "Samuel",
            "Thomas"
        ],
        "answer": "Thomas"
    },
    {
        "question": "How big is Eren's founding titan?",
        "answers": [
            "350 Meters",
            "300 Meters",
            "230 Meters",
            "235 Meters"
        ],
        "answer": "235 Meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sasha was supposed to die in season 2 but Isayama's editor changed his mind",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "13 no Fuyu (13 Winters) is Mikasa singing about her feelings towards Eren and his 13 year time limit",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Isayama has revealed before that he based Falco and Gabi's characters on popular American TV shows",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Hange's gender/pronouns in the manga?",
        "answers": [
            "She/her",
            "They/Them",
            "He/Him"
        ],
        "answer": "They/Them"
    },
    {
        "question": "Levi has a sleeping disorder",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the shortest character in the show?",
        "answers": [
            "Historia",
            "Levi",
            "Connie",
            "Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Historia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Isayama's favorite character is Reiner",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the tallest character in the show?",
        "answers": [
            "Bertholdt",
            "Yelena",
            "Jean",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Yelena"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reiner Braun's Armored titan is based on the body of former UFC heavyweight champion and professional wrestler Brock Lesnar",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How big is Rod Reiss' pure titan form?",
        "answers": [
            "150 Meters",
            "110 Meters",
            "130 Meters",
            "120 Meters"
        ],
        "answer": "120 Meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Historia drag through the snow to save in season 2?",
        "answers": [
            "Samuel",
            "Armin",
            "Daz",
            "Sasha"
        ],
        "answer": "Daz"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Historia's nickname given to her by her friends?",
        "answers": [
            "The Cattle-Farming Godess",
            "Godess of purity",
            "Godess of horses",
            "Goddess of beauty"
        ],
        "answer": "The Cattle-Farming Godess"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname Jean's mom calls him",
        "answers": [
            "Horseface",
            "Jeanboy",
            "Jeanie",
            "JeanJean"
        ],
        "answer": "Jeanboy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nickname was given to Sasha when she was in the trainee corps?",
        "answers": [
            "Potato girl",
            "Meat stealer",
            "Bread girl",
            "Ms.Gluttonous"
        ],
        "answer": "Potato girl"
    },
    {
        "question": "What village is Sasha from?",
        "answers": [
            "Dauper",
            "Ragako",
            "Jinae",
            "Mitras"
        ],
        "answer": "Dauper"
    },
    {
        "question": "What village is Marco from?",
        "answers": [
            "Dauper",
            "Ragako",
            "Jinae",
            "Mitras"
        ],
        "answer": "Jinae"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many of the 9 titans does Marley have under its control?",
        "answers": [
            "9",
            "4",
            "7",
            "5"
        ],
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Helos?",
        "answers": [
            "A Fabricated Marleyan hero",
            "A Marleyan legend",
            "A Marleyan warrior",
            "An Eldian"
        ],
        "answer": "A Fabricated Marleyan hero"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who ended the Great Titan war?",
        "answers": [
            "The Tyburs",
            "Karl Fritz"
        ],
        "answer": "Karl Fritz"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the 12th Commander of the Scout Regiment?",
        "answers": [
            "Keith Shadis",
            "Erwin Smith",
            "Hannes",
            "Hange Zoe"
        ],
        "answer": "Keith Shadis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the age requirement to become a warrior candidate?",
        "answers": [
            "15 years old",
            "12 years old",
            "9 years old",
            "10 years old"
        ],
        "answer": "12 years old"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which episode does Eren lose his arm?",
        "answers": [
            "First battle",
            "Whereabouts of his left arm",
            "Idol",
            "Night of the closing ceremony"
        ],
        "answer": "First battle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first hint we received that Eren was a titan shifter?",
        "answers": [
            "Steaming head",
            "Steaming hand",
            "Steaming arm",
            "Steaming foot"
        ],
        "answer": "Steaming head"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the top priority objective for the Yeagerists?",
        "answers": [
            "Yeager brothers touching to unlock founding titan's powers",
            "Eradication of all of humanity outside the walls",
            "Freedom for all Eldians",
            "Revenge against Marley"
        ],
        "answer": "Yeager brothers touching to unlock founding titan's powers"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many kids did Rod Reiss have?",
        "answers": [
            "7 children",
            "10 children",
            "4 children",
            "6 children"
        ],
        "answer": "6 children"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Isayama get the inspiration for Hange's character?",
        "answers": [
            "From a strange and endearing friend he once had",
            "From a TV show",
            "From a Japanese pop band",
            "From his job"
        ],
        "answer": "From a strange and endearing friend he once had"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two characters were orignally drafted to be the same character by Isayama?",
        "answers": [
            "Jean/Armin",
            "Mikasa/Annie",
            "Eren/Armin",
            "Connie/Sasha"
        ],
        "answer": "Jean/Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "The inspiration behind Eren's character is Isayama himself reflecting on the worst parts of himself",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which district is Jean from?",
        "answers": [
            "Trost",
            "Shiganshina",
            "Orvud",
            "Stohess"
        ],
        "answer": "Trost"
    },
    {
        "question": "What profession did Erwin's dad have?",
        "answers": [
            "Teacher",
            "Soldier",
            "Doctor",
            "Stohess"
        ],
        "answer": "Teacher"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Erwin have a love interest?",
        "answers": [
            "Yes, Her name was Marie and he gave her up so he can become a scout",
            "No, He's too much of a sigma male"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes, Her name was Marie and he gave her up so he can become a scout"
    },
    {
        "question": "Everyone listed below from the 104th cadet corps is an orphan EXCEPT:",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Historia",
            "Connie",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Jean"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times can a titan shifter transform?",
        "answers": [
            "Up to 3 times",
            "Up to 2 times",
            "Up to 5 times",
            "Infinite"
        ],
        "answer": "Up to 3 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Historia's fake name when she was in the cadet corps?",
        "answers": [
            "Krista Lenz",
            "Christine Fritz",
            "Florine Renz",
            "Kristine Lenz"
        ],
        "answer": "Krista Lenz"
    },
    {
        "question": "How long was Eren in Marley for?",
        "answers": [
            "10 months",
            "2 months",
            "6 months",
            "8 months"
        ],
        "answer": "10 months"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was controlling Marley from the shadows?",
        "answers": [
            "The Tyburs",
            "The mid-east forces",
            "Marley's military",
            "The Eldians"
        ],
        "answer": "The Tyburs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who led the coup d'etat against the corrupt royal nobles?",
        "answers": [
            "Pixis",
            "Erwin",
            "Zackly",
            "Nile"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of the armband worn by the Warriors?",
        "answers": [
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "White",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of the armband worn by Eldians in the internment zone?",
        "answers": [
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "White",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer": "White"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of the armband worn by Warrior cadets?",
        "answers": [
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "White",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Zeke's nickname?",
        "answers": [
            "Boy wonder",
            "Monkey",
            "Marley's shield",
            "Zook"
        ],
        "answer": "Boy wonder"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Reiner's nickname?",
        "answers": [
            "God of destruction",
            "Lainah",
            "Marley's shield",
            "Boy wonder"
        ],
        "answer": "Marley's shield"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people were killed during the failed operation to retake wall Maria in episode 2?",
        "answers": [
            "250,000",
            "400,000",
            "150,000",
            "120,000"
        ],
        "answer": "250,000"
    },
    {
        "question": "How tall is the Beast titan?",
        "answers": [
            "17 meters",
            "15 meters",
            "20 meters",
            "23 meters"
        ],
        "answer": "17 meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the protagonist of Before the fall?",
        "answers": [
            "Kuklo",
            "Eren",
            "Korko",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Kuklo"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the manga, Who gives Historia the idea of punching Levi?",
        "answers": [
            "Dimo Reeves",
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Dimo Reeves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mikasa's mother was supposed to give birth to a baby boy.",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "An Ackermann's power awakens when their survival instinct is triggered",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Titans are bizarly light for their immense size",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What new weapon was created to kill nearby titans at the end of Season 3?",
        "answers": [
            "Titan guillotine",
            "Anti-Personnel squad weapons",
            "Titan crusher",
            "Thunderspears"
        ],
        "answer": "Titan guillotine"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did Grisha give Eren the founding titan after telling Zeke to stop Eren?",
        "answers": [
            "He changed his mind after learning about carla's death and wanted Eren to avenge her",
            "He went insane",
            "He didn't care"
        ],
        "answer": "He changed his mind after learning about carla's death and wanted Eren to avenge her"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mikasa is worth a thousand ordinary soldiers.",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which squad was Floch assigned to in the Return to Shiganshina Arc?",
        "answers": [
            "Squad Klaus",
            "Squad Dirk",
            "Squad Levi",
            "Squad Marlene"
        ],
        "answer": "Squad Klaus"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the last chapter of the manga released?",
        "answers": [
            "April 2021",
            "March 2022",
            "October 2021",
            "August 2023"
        ],
        "answer": "April 2021"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the special chapter that is about Levi's Backstory?",
        "answers": [
            "Bad Boy",
            "No regrets",
            "Bad legacy",
            "Thug"
        ],
        "answer": "Bad Boy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following names is taken from Norse mythology?",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Eren",
            "Reiner",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has both Eldian and Marleyan blood?",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Zeke",
            "Porco",
            "Pieck"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Sasha save when Trost was breached?",
        "answers": [
            "Samuel",
            "Daz",
            "Nack",
            "Thomas"
        ],
        "answer": "Samuel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the Talking titan call Ilse Langnar?",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir-sama",
            "Ymir-san",
            "Goddess Ymir",
            "Freckles"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir-sama"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many commanders of the Survey corps has there been?",
        "answers": [
            "15",
            "13",
            "17",
            "16"
        ],
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "How tall is Annie's titan?",
        "answers": [
            "15 meters",
            "14 meters",
            "17 meters",
            "16 meters"
        ],
        "answer": "14 meters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal was Tom Ksaver's Beast titan?",
        "answers": [
            "Sheep",
            "Lamb",
            "Goat",
            "Bull"
        ],
        "answer": "Sheep"
    },
    {
        "question": "Floch believed in his devils",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If you win, you live. If you lose, you die. If you don't fight, you can't win.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Floch"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I Am Strong. Stronger Than All Of You. Extremely Strong. I Can Kill All The Titans Out There. Even If I Am Alone",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Sasha"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? The world is a cruel but it's also very beautiful",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Eren, Thank you for wrapping the scarf around me",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I don't have time to worry whether it's right or wrong. You can't hope for a horror story with a happy ending! Yeah, it's a cruel world out there.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Keep moving forward. Even if you die. Even after you die",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Our Devils are our only hope",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Floch",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I might be nothing more than a fodder. I'm sure my only purpose is to be expendable. But even a piece of fodder should at least have the right to call it like he sees it!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Floch",
            "Marlo",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? There's a devil inside of us all and that's why the world turned out this way.",
        "answers": [
            "Erwin",
            "Floch",
            "Nicolo",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Nicolo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If You Think It's Natural For People To Die For Others. I'm Sure You'll Understand That At Times, The Sacrifice Of A Single Precious Life Can Save Many Others",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Floch",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? My Speciality Is Carving Flesh. Anyone Interested In Experiencing My Skill Firsthand, Step Right Up.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? There are only so many lives that I actually care about. My Enemies made deciding that easy six years ago. So you're mistaken to seek any compassion from me. Because right now, I'm all out of time and room in my heart to care.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Once I'm dead, I won't even be able to remember you. So I'll win, no matter what. I'll live, no matter what!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? That's right… This world… is cruel. It hit me that living was like a miracle",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? A cruel world where only the victors can survive",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? That's right… This world… is cruel. It hit me that living was like a miracle",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? However, no matter the world you make, you cannot stop Eren's death. Because Death is ingrained within his body. No matter how much you try to protect him, death will snare him.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Mirror Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You must become strong and return to your world.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Mirror Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I am no one. And I am Everyone",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Mirror Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Mirror Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You are a lost child. Unable to accept Eren's death, you created this world to get lost in",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Mirror Man"
        ],
        "answer": "Mirror Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? We're all free from the moment we're born. It doesn't matter how strong the opposition is. There doesn't need to be flaming water or land made of ice. Those who witness the outside world are free like no other.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Fight. My life is second to that desire. It doesn't matter how fearsome the world is. It doesn't matter how cruel the world is. Fight.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If someone aims to take away my freedom, I won't hesitate to take away theirs first",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Ever since I was born...I've always been me",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Is it wrong not to be special? I don't think that way. When it comes to my child... it's fine if he's never great . He doesn't have to be better than anyone. After all, just look at him. He's so cute! He's already special. Because he was ... born into this world.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Carla",
            "Mikasa",
            "Kuchel"
        ],
        "answer": "Carla"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Because I was born into this world",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? What is the point if those with the means and power do not fight?",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Erwin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If you think reality is just living comfortably and following your own whims, can you seriously dare to call yourself a soldier",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Erwin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I can do this! No...we can do this! Because we've all been special since the day we were born! We're free!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I want to see and understand the world outside. I don't want to die inside these walls without knowing what's out there!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Nothing can suppress a human's curiosity",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Grisha"
        ],
        "answer": "Grisha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'll wrap it around you again... as many times as you want. Now and forever.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'm the same as you. I didn't have any other choice.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Connie",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You have the freedom to defend the world's freedom and I have the freedom to continue moving forward.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Grisha",
            "Ymir",
            "King Fritz"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'll kill them all! I'll wipe every last one of them off the face of this earth!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Ymir",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You damn traitors!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Connie",
            "Sasha",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If people knew it would come to this, nobody would go to war. But most people are pushed by something, forced to march into hell. That 'something' wasn't their choice. Their situation or others made them do it. But people who push their own backs see a different kind of hell. They can see something beyond the hell. It might be hope. It may even be another hell. Only those who keep moving forward will ever know.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? There's no time to figure out if this the right thing to do! Just move - Don't try to keep your hands clean. That's right, the world is cruel.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? No matter how messed up things get, you can always figure out the best solution.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I disposed of some dangerous beasts. Mere animals that just happened to resemble humans.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? It's not me or the commander who's going to save humanity. It's Armin!!",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'm free. No matter what I do or how I do it, I'm acting of my own free will.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You're all free.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Ymir",
            "Reiner",
            "King Fritz"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Even if I'm dead, their lives will go on. I want them to live long, happy lives.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Hange",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I knew you were more of a hero than anyone else",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Jean",
            "Hange"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Because I'm an Idiot. A garden variety idiot who got his hands on power.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin",
            "Porco"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You're Only Resorting To Physical Abuse Because You Can't Prove That I'm Wrong",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Falco"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Those who can't abandon anything, can't change anything",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? In order to rise above monsters you must be willing to throw aside your humanity.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Erwin",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? From the day I was born they were always just there, wherever I looked... those miserable walls. Flaming water, land made of ice and sandy snowfields..",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'd rather die than become a burden",
        "answers": [
            "Connie",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I don't like the terms good person or bad person because it is impossible to be entirely good to everyone. To some, you are a good person, while to others, you are a bad person.",
        "answers": [
            "Connie",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I refuse to standby with clean hands",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Jean",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? The world hasn't become hell...It's always been hell where the strong feed upon weak. It's such an obligingly simple rule. Except in this world, my friends tried to be strong.",
        "answers": [
            "Marco",
            "Jean",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I think there are times people have to die... even if I don't like it.",
        "answers": [
            "Sasha",
            "Jean",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I am a soldier! And I have dedicated my heart to the restoration of humanity. Nothing would make me prouder than dying for such a noble cause!",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Erwin",
            "Armin",
            "Keith"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? We're going to explore the outside world someday, right? Far beyond these walls, there's flaming water, land made of ice, and fields of san spread wide",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Isabel",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You know, because I'm just not the hero type.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Jean",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I didn't lose, because I didn't run.",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Connie",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? When people are faced with a situation they don't understand, it's easy for fear to take hold",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Connie",
            "Armin",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? But with enough time, If we set aside our labels and see each other as people, we can understand each other.",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Yelena",
            "Armin",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Eren, In what way are you free?",
        "answers": [
            "Mikasa",
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? We'll suffer for the sin of killing eighty percent of humanity, Together.",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Everyone Had To Be Drunk On Somethin' To Keep Pushing On … Everyone Was A Slave To Somethin'",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Kenny",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Kenny"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? We've got to keep the young-uns out of the forest. Otherwise, ain't nothin' gonna stop it from happening again. That's why it's up to us adults to shoulder the sins of the past.",
        "answers": [
            "Sasha",
            "Mr. Braus",
            "Kenny",
            "Nicolo"
        ],
        "answer": "Mr. Braus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Escape the forest. Even if we can't, we've gotta keep trying",
        "answers": [
            "Sasha",
            "Mr. Braus",
            "Kenny",
            "Nicolo"
        ],
        "answer": "Nicolo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I've killed a lot of people. So that people would praise me. That's the devil within me",
        "answers": [
            "Bertholdt",
            "Gabi",
            "Reiner",
            "Annie"
        ],
        "answer": "Gabi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Give up on your dream and die.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Pixis",
            "Nile",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Even if I believe in myself, or the choices of my trusted comrades but no one ever knows how it will turn out. You should just do your best to make a decision you won't regret. ",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Hange",
            "Miche",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? No casualties, Don't you dare die!",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Hange",
            "Miche",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Don't get me wrong you will never be Erwin's replacement but... I know you have a strength that nobody else has but you,",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Hange",
            "Floch",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? The world without titans we dreamed of was supposed to be an astoundngly joyful place. An Ideal world.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Hange",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Don't, you'll regret it. If you begin to regret it, you'll dull your future decisions and let others make your choices for you",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Hange",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Nobody can foretell the outcome, therefore, each decision you make, holds meaning only be effecting your next decision.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Hange",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Everything that you thought had meaning: Every hope, dream, or moment of happiness. None of it matters as you lie bleeding out on the battlefield. None of it changes what a speeding rock does to a body, we all die.",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Hange",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? My soldiers push forward! My soldiers scream out! My soldiers RAAAAAGE!",
        "answers": [
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Hange",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? One day, We'll Break it down. This Wall hiding the truth will fall.",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Eren",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? There Is No Future Where Humanity Can Inhabit These Lands Without Eren.",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Levi",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Humanity will never stop fighting itself until it shrinks to a size of one or fewer",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Pixis",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? When necessary, We must be willing to take big risks, and be prepared to lose everything.",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Pixis",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Can you see them too? Our comrades… They are all standing around us. They have been watching us all this time… They wanna know what we did with the sacrifices that they made…What became of the hearts they gave… But that's probably just in my head, right?",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Erwin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? But is pride worth dying for? What's so wrong with submission? Isn't it better than dying like this?",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Connie",
            "Jean",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If Eren dies, Paradis will drown in a sea of blood",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Connie",
            "Jean",
            "Hange"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? The one who will save Eldia is...me!",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Hange"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I can't kick the bucket just yet. Eldia's restoration is finally at hand",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Samuel",
            "Jean",
            "Daz"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it?  I didn't care if people lived or died. I didn't think any life had value, including my own",
        "answers": [
            "Armin",
            "Annie",
            "Jean",
            "Gabi"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I wish I could've stayed locked up in my room with my ears covered but...those ashes of the dead would never forgive me.",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Jean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If we run and hide, What will we have left?",
        "answers": [
            "Hange",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Levi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? A know-it-all wouldn't get how idiots work",
        "answers": [
            "Connie",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Sasha"
        ],
        "answer": "Connie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I wanna be a soldier my mom could take pride in",
        "answers": [
            "Connie",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Sasha"
        ],
        "answer": "Connie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Genocide is wrong! There is no reason to commend such an act!",
        "answers": [
            "Connie",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Hange"
        ],
        "answer": "Hange"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Nothing can take the violence out of people. Right Captain?",
        "answers": [
            "Yelena",
            "Armin",
            "Onyankopon",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Yelena"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I am a descendant of Royal blood!",
        "answers": [
            "Zeke",
            "Dina",
            "Rod",
            "Frieda"
        ],
        "answer": "Zeke"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'll Free The People Of The World From Their Fear Of The Titans And I'll Free The Eldians From Their Suffering.",
        "answers": [
            "Zeke",
            "Grisha",
            "Floch",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Zeke"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? It Isn't Your Fault That We Were Born To That Disgusting Monster Of A Man. I will fix you with the Founding titan's power.",
        "answers": [
            "Zeke",
            "Ymir",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Zeke"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? What nice weather... If only I had thought of that eariler well.. I suppose that's too much to ask for after all the killing I've done",
        "answers": [
            "Zeke",
            "Ymir",
            "Annie",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Zeke"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'll be waiting for you. In hell.",
        "answers": [
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa",
            "Zeke",
            "Eren"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You traitors! Aren't we all friends?!",
        "answers": [
            "Samuel",
            "Daz",
            "Floch",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Samuel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Someone has to be the one to stain their hands with blood",
        "answers": [
            "Bertholdt",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Bertholdt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? This sure is a peculiar feeling. I'm not scared at all for once. And I see everything clearly",
        "answers": [
            "Bertholdt",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin",
            "Jean"
        ],
        "answer": "Bertholdt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? None Of You Have Done Anything Wrong. And You're Not Devils. It's Just That You All Have To Die. That's just the way it is.",
        "answers": [
            "Bertholdt",
            "Reiner",
            "Zeke",
            "Gabi"
        ],
        "answer": "Bertholdt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Defend our island to the death! Our country!",
        "answers": [
            "Floch",
            "Samuel",
            "Daz",
            "Magath"
        ],
        "answer": "Floch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? The only sure way to end this cycle of revenge fueled by hate is to bury our hate filled history along with civilization itself",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Erwin",
            "Hange",
            "Floch"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'm starting to hate all of humanity! I say let them get wiped out by Titans! And if that makes me an enemy of humanity, so be it! I don't care if I'm the worst girl who ever lived!",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Historia",
            "Mikasa",
            "Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Historia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'll fight them with you, so let me out of your hand! I don't care if there's something you can't tell me. No matter what happens... I will always be your ally!",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Historia",
            "Mikasa",
            "Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Historia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? It's wrong to make you bear the sins of the past due to your race",
        "answers": [
            "Yelena",
            "Magath",
            "Onyankopon",
            "Gabi"
        ],
        "answer": "Magath"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Going against the flow... takes a lot of courage. I respect that. Maybe people who can do it are just stupid, but... Well... What I'm sure of is that people like that are rare. So you can't call them common. You can't call them normal, either. People like you... get called special.",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Hitch",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If Somebody Told You To Die, Would You",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Hitch",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I Guess You Were Lucky That I Was A Good Person To You. It Looks Like Your Gamble Paid Off For Now But This Is Where Mine Begins",
        "answers": [
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Pieck",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I want to survive and see her again. As a person, I'm really lower than sh*t, but she knows that, and she smiles kindly at me anyway.",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Annie",
            "Sasha",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? There was one thing I wished for with all my heart. If I'm ever given a second chance in life, I want to live for only myself. That is my sincere wish.",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Do you always want to live hiding behind the mask you put up for the sake of others? You're you, and there's nothing wrong with that",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Annie",
            "Mikasa",
            "Historia"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? If We Turn Our Back On Hunting We Turn Our Back On Who We Are",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Sasha",
            "Jean",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Sasha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? When I learned that humanity lived outside the walls... I was so disappointed.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Jean",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I...would choose to have never been born, if it was up to me. I've hated my blood. More than anyone else...I wished for the extinction of all Eldians. ...but I do not wish to die. Because...I was born into this world.",
        "answers": [
            "Willy",
            "Zeke",
            "Gabi",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Willy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I...would choose to have never been born, if it was up to me. I've hated my blood. More than anyone else...I wished for the extinction of all Eldians. ...but I do not wish to die. Because...I was born into this world.",
        "answers": [
            "Willy",
            "Zeke",
            "Gabi",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Willy"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many MMA fighters is Eren's titan modeled after?",
        "answers": [
            "Five",
            "Three",
            "Four",
            "Two"
        ],
        "answer": "Two"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cart titan in the Return to Shiganshina Arc looked different compared to the duck billed one that we are used to",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pieck Could Have Been A Middle-Aged Man named Oliver originally",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Levi forces Hange to bathe by knocking her out and doing it by force",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mikasa takes her scarf off whenever it is too hot and she takes well care of it by washing it as well with warm water",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Levi care so much about cleanliness?",
        "answers": [
            "Because he lived in a filthy brothel with his mother",
            "Because his mother influenced him",
            "Because he's traumatized by the filth in the underground city"
        ],
        "answer": "Because he lived in a filthy brothel with his mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Isayama base Mikasa's appearance off of?",
        "answers": [
            "While working his part-time job at a net cafe, He saw a women with a scarf and hairstyle and eyes like Mikasa",
            "From his childhood friend",
            "From a different anime"
        ],
        "answer": "While working his part-time job at a net cafe, He saw a women with a scarf and hairstyle and eyes like Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yuki Kaji Had A Special Ritual While Recording Eren's Lines, Which was...",
        "answers": [
            "Wearing the same underwear each time",
            "Wearing the same shirt each time",
            "Saying tatakae to himself in the mirror before recording",
            "Biting his hand each time"
        ],
        "answer": "Wearing the same underwear each time"
    },
    {
        "question": "It took Arifumi Imai Four Months To Animate The Levi Vs. Beast Titan Fight in the RTS Arc",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Isayama Always Intended For Eren To Become A Villain",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Levi strangles Historia in the manga and forces her to become the queen",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was first to discover the female titan's true identity?",
        "answers": [
            "Erwin",
            "Armin",
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the real life worm that Isayama took inspiration from for the source of all living matter that Ymir came into contact with?",
        "answers": [
            "Hallucigenia",
            "Anomalocaris",
            "Opabinia",
            "Tullimonstrum"
        ],
        "answer": "Hallucigenia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I don't know why but when it comes to taking back freedom...Strength flows through me",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? For some reason, when I think of the outside world, courage flows through me",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Armin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I've never heard of a titan killing another titan. I felt a glimmer of exhilaration... I felt the rage of humanity itself was embodied in what I saw",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Armin",
            "Levi",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? You Do What You Have To Do. Just Keep Moving. That's How It Works, Right?",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Reiner",
            "Hange",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Reiner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'm Sick And Tired Of Walls.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Reiner",
            "Armin",
            "Mikasa"
        ],
        "answer": "Reiner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I hope you won't get mad when I say this... But you aren't a strong person. so you can relate to how the weak feel. In addition, you excel in sizing up any situation. Isn't that why you immediately know what should be done?",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Marco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Why Are You In Such A Rush? We Haven't Even Had A Chance To Talk This Over!",
        "answers": [
            "Jean",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Levi"
        ],
        "answer": "Marco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? Most humans are weak, including me... but if i got an order from someone who saw things as I do... No matter how tough it was, I'd do my damnedest to carry it out",
        "answers": [
            "Jean",
            "Marco",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Marco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I have no right to tell you how to live your life. So actually this is nothing more than a hope of mine. I want you to live a life you're proud of",
        "answers": [
            "Ymir",
            "Levi",
            "Armin",
            "Connie"
        ],
        "answer": "Ymir"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? When I became a titan I thought nothing of it. I wanted to believe that strength was all mine. That's exactly how a weakling thinks.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Annie",
            "Armin",
            "Reiner"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? It might not be all they hoped for, but now.. Humanity has an ace up its sleeve.",
        "answers": [
            "Eren",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Erwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Eren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said it? I'm sorry Eren I won't give up anymore. Once I'm dead, I won't even be able to remember you. So I'll win, no matter what. I'll live, no matter what!",
        "answers": [
            "Historia",
            "Mikasa",
            "Armin",
            "Ymir"
        ],
        "answer": "Mikasa"
    }
]